A Guide to the Theodore Malinin collection of Alexis Carrel and Charles Lindbergh papers FA208
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Slides-Carrel/Malinin, 1914-1977; 6; 0.8 Cubic Feet
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [color] (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Carrel Slides: WWI Medical Slides [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Carrel Slides: Vascular Suturing [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Carrel Slides: Vascular Suturing, [black & white], 1910-1912 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Carrel Slides: Carrel Portraits [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Carrel Slides: Carrel Personal - France [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Carrel Slides: Carrel Personal - France [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Carrel Slides: Carrel Personal - France [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Carrel Slides: Carrel Personal - France [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Carrel Slides: Carrel Personal - France [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Malinin Slides: Presentation & Perfusion Pump [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Malinin Slides: Presentation & Perfusion Pump [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Malinin Slides: Presentation & Perfusion Pump [black & white] (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Malinin Slides: Presentation & Perfusion Pump [black & white/ color] (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Reprints, 1904-1985; 7; 0.6 Cubic Feet
  Contains reprints of both Carrel and colleagues and associates with whom he worked over the years. There are also miscellaneous reprints.
  The Carrel reprints are arranged in alphabetical order, whilst the reprints of his colleagues are arranged in chronological order.
  - Reprints: Carrel - A-I (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Reprints: Carrel - L-Z (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Reprints: Carrel Colleagues, 1907-1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Reprints: Miscellaneous Reprints & Articles (Box 19, Folder 3)